<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DM Thinking</title>
    <link>https://dpmdm.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DM Thinking</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 18:27:58 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dpmdm.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Compliance as code</title>
      <link>https://dpmdm.github.io/blog/compliance-as-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 10:39:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dpmdm.github.io/blog/compliance-as-code/</guid>
      <description>What is compliance as code and why to use it?
First lets start with the compliance stuff.
 Compliance is the state of being in accordance with established guidlines or specifications, or the process of becoming so.
 From https://www.techtarget.com/searchdatamanagement/definition/compliance
That says that there will be certain types of rules that we want to follow. When we follow these rules or strive to follow, we are compliant.
Compliance in organisations Historically companies and organisations have manual process to verify that teams are following the rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technique</title>
      <link>https://dpmdm.github.io/blog/technique/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:29:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dpmdm.github.io/blog/technique/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know why, but I have always seen documentation as critical part of software engineering. Not only as helpful comments in the code, but also to document the infrastructure and way-of-working.
Some times I wonder if IT and archeology should be more connected. So many times knowledge are hidden by employees. All these time consuming handovers when people quit or change positions.
The other side is that I have a short memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Method</title>
      <link>https://dpmdm.github.io/blog/method/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 16:31:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dpmdm.github.io/blog/method/</guid>
      <description>Is it a good to try to exaplain how this site will grow&amp;hellip;.
My initial thinking is that I will collect my &amp;ldquo;knowledge&amp;rdquo; into
 blog posts articles  It would be great if the blog post can in some way lead to articles. Is it possilby to see the blogs as &amp;ldquo;behind the scenes&amp;rdquo; of the articles?
Hm&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start</title>
      <link>https://dpmdm.github.io/blog/initial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 04:05:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dpmdm.github.io/blog/initial/</guid>
      <description>Why not start to write down my thoughts in a blog?
I see my self as 30 years old.
 A decade when I grown up A decade with studies A decade with work  That will sum up to 20 years of thinking about software engineering. But what would the purpose of it be?
 If someone will read it, that&amp;rsquo;s great! I can show my family why I&amp;rsquo;m sitting up late Get my own material of the things I work on  Thats it, I will do it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://dpmdm.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dpmdm.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer that has a passion for understanding and connecting the dots.
My programming journey This is a presentation of my learning path when we talk about programming.
 BASIC     This was the first programming langugae I tried out. Inital I copied a game from a book. It took horrible long time to complete.
The game was played as a bat. To complete the game the bat needed to eat up all bugs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
